



# Тимофеев Кирилл

Male, 28 years, born on 10 July 1991

+7 (917) 1920467

veefomit llirik@mail.ru — preferred means of communication

Reside in: Astrakhan

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia Not ready to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

# .net Developer

IT, Internet, Telecom

- Software Development
- Web Engineer

Employment: full time

Work schedule: remote working Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 5 years 9 months

November 2019 till now 7 months

# **PARMA Technologies Group**

www.parma.ru/

#### .net developer

Full-stack developer (c#) - developing automated system of law statistics for Russia General Prosecutor's Office

Responsibilities - development new features, system improvement and fixing bugs.

Technologies:

Frontend - asp .net web forms + jQuery + kendo ui, Angular 8.

Backend - asp .net mvc, WebAPI, REST, Owin, unit testing - NUnit, DI - Unity (later SimpleInjector)

DB: Oracle 12

October 2016 — October 2019 3 years 1 month

## **ООО Macтep-Areнt (MAG.Travel)**

www.mag.travel/

## .net developer

Full-stack developer (c#) - development CRM system for tour agencies, development and maintance of hotel/avia search + booking service,

Responsibilities - development new features, system improvement, bug fixing, deployment services (on client servers), maintance services, system speed optimization.

Technologies.

Project #1:

Frontend - jQuery, later some parts were made on Vue.js.

Backend - asp .net mvc (some parts on asp .net core), WCF, SOAP, REST, Quartz.NET, Ninject, Owin,

Entity Framework (+ some raw SQL), asp .net identity

DB: MS SQL

Project #2:

Frontend - one project asp .net web forms + jQuery Backend - asp .net mvc, SOAP, REST, Entity Framework

DB: MS SQL

September 2014 — October 2016 2 years 2 months

# Бест-софт

## 1C programmer

Creating and maintenance configurations on 1С Предприятие platform.

#### Education

#### Master

2014 Astrahan State University, Astrakhan

Mathematics and IT, Information Technology (master)

2012 Astrahan State University, Astrakhan

Mathematics and IT, Information Technology (bachelor)

## Key skills

Languages Russian — Native

English — B2 — Upper Intermediate

Skills C# MVC MS SQL Server JavaScript TypeScript ORACLE ASP.NET

Software Development .net core Angular REST SOAP Ajax

Entity Framework LINQ

#### Further information

About me

Experienced Software Engineer with a history of working in the internet industry.

- \* Knowledge of software design patterns
- \* General knowledge of JavaScript, Angular, JQuery
- \* Experience in working with SOAP, WCF, REST
- \* Ability to write clean code
- \* Experience in profiling and optimizing performance
- \* Good knowledge of OOP
- \* Knowledge of DI/IoC and experience of use it
- \* Understanding of async/await
- \* Experience in EF and Ling
- \* Knowledge of SQL and general knowledge T-SQL

Experience in working with this tools: LINQPad, Postman, Soap UI, Fiddler, dnSpy/dotPeek, VS Studio 2013/2017/2019, VS Code, SSMS. Some experience administrating applications in IIS.

Control-version systems: TFS, Git

Technologies: WCF, ASP.NET, MS Sql Server, Entity Framework, .Net Core, ELK, Quartz.NET, Linq to Sql, Windows Forms, WebAPI, OracleDB

Personal skills:

\* Responsibility.

- \* Discipline.
- \* Desire to improving myself and learn new
- \* Stress resistance